<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>tech on Uncombed Whiskers</title>
    <link>/categories/tech/</link>
    <description>Recent content in tech on Uncombed Whiskers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 09:01:32 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/tech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Threat Horizons</title>
      <link>/post/threat_horizons_sep22/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 09:01:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/threat_horizons_sep22/</guid>
      <description>Latest Threat Horizons report from Google Cloud is out!
Insights These are a few insights from it.
57.4% Cloud Compromises are due to weak or no credentials You&amp;rsquo;ve got to be kidding me! It&amp;rsquo;s 2022 for Pete&amp;rsquo;s sake!
At least use STRONG password and MFA, if nothing else!
65% of Compromises are used for Crypto Mining A bit surprising but it is what it is. SSH, WordPress, and RDP are most targeted Not surprized at all!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week1</title>
      <link>/post/week1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 11:01:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/week1/</guid>
      <description>As the first week at the new gig draws to a close, the total absurdity (in a very good way) of the development, build &amp;amp; deploy system here just blows my mind.
I do not know if this is something I know enough about to discuss at this time or if that&amp;rsquo;s even allowed (you know NDA and such), but I can say for sure that the immense amount of engineer time &amp;amp; productivity lost in my last gig could have been salvaged - if only we had spent enough time thinking about &amp;amp; working on reducing the build &amp;amp; deploy times over the years, instead of sitting on our haunches, patting our backs &amp;amp; basking in the light of past laurels 😞</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
